Nick Beeson

Nick_beeson@yahoo.com | 720-635-9460 | 2575 S Syracuse Way Denver, CO 80231

SUMMARY

I am a senior at the University of Denver enrolled in the engineering and computer science course. I have been programming for years, 4 years academically, and about a year professionally. Outside of class, I have been a VEX robotics team captain, competed in several game jams, president of the University of Denver Game Developers' Society, and creator of the annual DU Arcade indie game expo.

COMPUTER SKILLS

Languages

- · Good with C#, Javascipt, Bash, mySQL
- Familiar with HTML5, Java, C++, Python

Software

- Unity: Proficient in game development and programming
- Microsoft Office: Know my way around the Office suite
- Use both Linux and Windows operating systems
- · Familiar with Git
- Web development frameworks: NodeJs, Angular, Express

EXPERIENCE

Hardware Intern Summer 2014

MSITec

- Built several hundred hardware assemblies for company customers
- · Worked briefly with Baxter from Rethink Robotics

Customer Service Representative

June 2015- August 2016, January 2017-present

GX2 Technology

- Took customer calls and assisted with hardware, troubleshooting connections, etc.
- Managed support call tickets
- · Worked with hotel staff to fix hardware issues remotely
- · Configured everything from switches to servers
- Learned basic networking

EDUCATION

University of Denver

2014-2018

- Applied Computing Major-BA
- Business Administration Minor
- Graduate June 2018